<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Android Hell]]></title>
  <link href="http://http://androidhell.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://http://androidhell.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-12-17T17:12:17+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://http://androidhell.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ralkkai]]></name>
    
  </author>

  
  <entry>
    
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's do this thing!]]></title>
    <link href="http://androidhell.github.io/blog/2015/12/17/lets-do-this-thing/"/>
    
    <updated>2015-12-17T15:01:40+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://http://androidhell.github.io/blog/2015/12/17/lets-do-this-thing</id>
    
      <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So first thing is first. I need to finish the about page for this thing.</p>

<p>On to business though. I think I can see myself using this to get my thoughts out. I really do like the hacky feeling of using cli and an ide in order to create blog posts instead of a wysiwyg.</p>

<p>I donno if I can post on a daily basis but it would be nice to use this as a sort of personal journal to see how things progress.</p>

<p>I can leave my America: The Shit Show blog as is instead of converting it over to this format. That space will be better suited for just typing things out, where this will be better suited for techy stuff.</p>

<p>Which is what I suppose it was initially meant for.</p>

<p>Before I do the tech stuff tho&hellip;</p>

<p>News Years Resolution idea:</p>

<ul>
<li>Be nicer to my enemies</li>
<li>drink less</li>
<li>focus on a single group of languages and actually focus on code logic (I&rsquo;ve been all over the place this year. [See: Pounds to Babies converter written in PHP])</li>
<li>Don&rsquo;t sweat the small stuff</li>
<li>Quit being politically loud on social media (change out the Hitler Trump Twitter pic)</li>
<li>155 lbs goal</li>
<li>take more photos. Hopefully the photography class will light that fire</li>
<li>Get a damn job. Anyone need websites made?</li>
<li>think of more things</li>
</ul>


<p>The list will be altered before the year is out. My main focus on the next year is to just avoid dickish people and to not be, myself, dickish. I&rsquo;m going to help out more too.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s looking like the web design business is not picking up and isn&rsquo;t at all where I was hoping it would be at this point. I&rsquo;m waiting out these next few weeks at FP and then I donno what I&rsquo;m going to do after that.</p>

<p>I might sleep until school starts again. Maybe play some games. I&rsquo;m in the middle of Deponia and it makes me feel dumb. I still haven’t done my annual Half-Life-athon or Mass Effect run.</p>

<p>EDIT: I also  need to figure out how to make this octopress thing my own since it is showing that I have done 860+ commits but those are from other people. I think I need to do a manual install instead of downloading it from git through command line.</p>

<p>-Ralkkai</p>
]]></content>
      
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title>
    <link href="http://androidhell.github.io/blog/2015/12/16/hello-world/"/>
    
    <updated>2015-12-16T18:37:05+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://http://androidhell.github.io/blog/2015/12/16/hello-world</id>
    
      <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my first post so I felt it was obvious that I should title it &ldquo;Hello World.&rdquo;</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m hoing to use this as my official platform for writing out my experiences in the programming world.</p>

<p>If this dies, then it dies.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m going to work on setting up this site&rsquo;s styling and get a proper about me page up before I delve further into things.</p>

<p>This will aslo be a chance for me to further explore markdown since my knowledge is limited to what little I have done on github and commenting on reddit.</p>

<p>Until I have mroe to say I will leve off at this point.</p>

<p>This is my attempt a maintaining a developer space on my github via Octopress, basically because it&rsquo;s cool and all the hipsters are gonna be jealous of my hacky blog skills.</p>

<p>At that, I say, Goodbye World!</p>
]]></content>
      
  </entry>
  
</feed>
